sunnypages.jp 2012-12-29

# Privacy Info - SunnyPages.jp

### Privacy on Sunnypages.jp - An Overview

ACTIVE corporation is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of consumers of its interactive products and services. Throughout cyberspace, we want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for consumers.

The purpose of this Sunnypages.jp privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor to Sunnypages.jp, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit Sunnypages.jp, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. Finally, please note that this policy applies only to Sunnupages.jp, and not to other companies' or organizations' Web sites to which we link.

### Information About All Sunnypages.jp Visitors

In general, our site automatically gathers certain usage information like the numbers and frequency of visitors to Sunnypages.jp and its areas, very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use such data in the aggregate. This aggregate data helps us determine how much our customers use parts of the site, so we can improve our site to assure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many of you as possible. For example, AOL.com uses a technology nicknamed "cookies" that tells us how and when pages in our site are visited, and by how many people. These cookies do not collect personally identifiable information and we do not combine information collected through these cookies with other personally identifiable information to tell us who you are or even what your screen name or e-mail address is. We also may provide statistical "ratings" information, never information about you personally, to our Sunnypages.jp partners about how our members, collectively, use Sunnypages.jp. We do this so they too can understand how much people use their areas and our site in order for them to provide you with the best possible Web experience as well. 

### Disclosure

We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to Sunnypages.jp or information that you may give us on Sunnypages.jp, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any outside companies. Sunnypages.jp may share such information in response to legal process, such as a court order or subpoena, or in special cases such as a physical threat to you or others. And, as we mention above, we may share with our Web site partners aggregated statistical "ratings" information about the use of Sunnypages.jp.

### Notification of Changes 

This Privacy Policy may be revised over time as our business grows and evolves. We will post any new privacy policy, along with the date of its last revision, prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check the Sites regularly for information about revisions to our privacy policy.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us.

Last updated: November 1st , 2006
